https://brana.org/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
MENUMENUHomeMeetingsNew to NA?NA GroupsCleanTimeJust for TodayFor the ProfessionalContact
Privacy Policy
BRANA respects the privacy of those who use our website. This privacy policy addresses concerns about how personally identifiable information (PII) is being used online. PII is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate an individual. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, and protect your personally identifiable information within our website https://brana.org and https://brana.org.
What personal information do we collect? When registering on our site you may be asked to enter your name, email address, home group, area, clean date, etc.
How do we use your information? The information we collect from you is used in the following ways:
You must provide your name and email address to contact usBeing registered gives you the fullest use of this WebsiteAfter you have registered, you may receive email alerts when new information is posted
How do we protect your information? There is no such thing as a 100-percent secure Website. However, we make every attempt to work with the most secure software available and take sensible precautions as Website administrators.This Website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes, malware, and vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible.Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who administer this Website and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all credit and sensitive information that you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.
As Website administrators, we follow these five principles of Website security:
Update all software regularlyDelete redundant files and extensionsCreate unique and difficult passwordsManage administrator accessMake regular backups
Third Party Disclosure: We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer your personally identifiable information to any outside parties.
Fair Information Practice: The Fair Information Practice Principles establish the essence of privacy law in the United States. To comply with FIPP, we agree to the following:
Notify our Website users via email within 7 business days should a data breach occur.Individual redress principle – Individuals may pursue legally enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law.Individuals have recourse to courts or government agencies to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.
SPAM: The CAN-SPAM Act (Controlling the Assault of Non-Solicited Pornography And Marketing) sets the rules for email, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped, and spells out penalties for violations. To be in accordance with CAN-SPAM we agree to the following:
We will not disseminate false or misleading informationWe will honor opt-out or unsubscribe requests promptly
Contact Us: If you have any questions regarding this privacy policy, please contact us using the contact form or by U.S. Post:Blue Ridge ASCP.O. BOX 289, Verona, VA 24482
Contact Us
Close Menu
MENUMENUHomeMeetingsNew to NA?NA GroupsCleanTimeJust for TodayFor the ProfessionalContact
